What on earth is that thing...
Let's run!
Wait!
We might get killed.
What do you suggest we do then?
Is there no other way out?
How would I know?
Two people are already dead.
Everyone. don't move.
If we move rashly.
the statue will attack again!
Joohee.
That was close.
If you didn't notice
the statue's movement.
we'd all be dead by now.
What?
You told us to get down
because you knew it. right?
No.
I just sensed an imminent threat...
Mr. Song!
Your hand...
I can still bear it.
Can you help me stop the bleeding?
I should have asked Joohee to treat me.
But she's too weak-minded.
That's why she can only participate in
simple missions
despite being a B-Rank healer.
I've also participated in
a couple of B-rank missions.
But that thing might be an A-rank one.
or even an S-rank one.
The commandments of the Cartenon Temple
written on the stone.
First. worship the God.
Second. praise the God.
Third. believe the God.
Those who do not abide
by these commandments
will not leave this place alive.
Mr. Song.
The god mentioned
should be it. right?
More than a decade ago.
portals that could connect to a different
dimension suddenly appeared in the world.
Abnormal phenomena kept
occurring around the world.
For example. The Awakened
are known as hunters.
Hunters are responsible for killing magic
beasts in dungeons within the portals.
And after hunters awaken.
their abilities will not change.
However. sometimes on
the other side of the portal.
there are terrifying monsters
that bring despair.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Did you see that?
That film?
What are you doing?
Class is about to start.
Something came up.
Jinah. your brother is a hunter. right?
Right.
But he's just an E-rank hunter.
He always ends up being covered in wounds.
Last time he was covered in bandages.
But why do you ask me this?
No reason.
If it were me. I wouldn't
have ended up like that.
We can't possibly be its opponent.
Let's get out once
the situation settles down.
- Although it might not be that easy...
- I can't just sit here and die!
I finally managed to sign a contract
with a large association.
I can't die in this kind of place.
What are you doing? Don't move!
I can do it.
I'm very confident in my speed.
I can rush out before it attacks.
Damn it!
It can finish us off at any time.
As easy as crushing an ant.
So why isn't it doing it now?
It has the ability to kill us.
but it isn't making a move.
It's different from those magic beasts
that attack blindly.
Mr. Song.
What is the first commandment?
Commandment?
The first one is...
Worship the God.
God.
This dungeon has its own rules.
What... what are you doing?
If I'm not wrong...
Hey. stop it...
You don't look like you're seeking death.
Everyone.
Kneel to the statue!
Huh? Kneel to it?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Did you figure out something?
Yes.
As long as our heads are below
a certain height. it won't attack.
This is probably the meaning
of the first commandment.
Are you sure?
Yes. sort of...
If so...
Will we really survive
by just doing this?
Its expression is terrifying.
Its expression changed.
It's not attacking us.
Hey. if you move around...
Look.
it has stopped attacking.
Is it over just like that?
Are we saved?
We made it.
We're saved.
I can go back alive.
No...
It's not over yet.
It's not over?
Sung. what's next?
Can you think of something?
I... I don't know.
I think we can't violate
the commandments here.
The second commandment
is "Praise the God".
This is the clue.
Praise?
How?
Leave it to me.
I am conducting research
on traditional folklore.
I know how to praise God.
Lord.
The ruler who brings order to the world.
Any reaction?
- Bestow your light upon my feeble heart.
- It seems to have slowed down...
Guide me to the path of truth.
Wait!
This is...
I wish to follow the will of God.
These are not the words
to praise this god.
We will worship and honor you.
Lord.
The ruler who brings order to the world.
Damn it!
Run!
It's dangerous to be together.
Scatter!
Alright.
Joohee. run!
How can I die in a place like this?
My family is still waiting for me!
I should be safe here. right?
Hey. Park. behind you!
Park!
Praise the God...
What should we praise about it?
It's essentially a demon.
But...
I can't just abandon her.
Is there any clue...
Gun.
Axe.
My hand... my hand!
Hammer.
Sword.
Musical instrument.
Musical instrument...
Everyone. get under the statue
holding a musical instrument!
Musical instrument.
Is it playing?
The statue holding a musical
instrument won't attack us!
Damn it.
Start playing quickly!
Come on!
Two people can't stand here together?
Joohee. stay here!
Jinwoo!
Over there.
Not there!
No!
Jinwoo!
It's not over yet.
It's not...
Is this the answer to praise the God?
Jinwoo!
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
Jinwoo.
What is the matter?
Your foot...
It's enough. Joohee.
I'm okay now.
What are you talking about?
I'll definitely cure you.
Joohee.
So tragic...
Indeed.
I'm very sorry that you lost your arm.
As the captain. you made a hasty decision.
This is karma.
How cruel.
It's because Mr. Kim...
Wasn't it a unanimous decision to come in?
You voted in favor. didn't you?
Indeed. it was me who
made the final decision.
I must bear all the responsibility.
Now is not the time to argue.
There is still one commandment
that has not been solved.
What's happening this time?
An earthquake?
What... What is that?
An altar...
Doesn't it often appear in mythology?
It's for offering tributes
or living sacrifices to the god.
The third commandment
is "Believe the God".
I might be ignorant. but I know
what this means.
Sung.
We need to offer a sacrifice. right?
My companion. who bragged about his wife
before departure. was cut in half.
There were others too.
Do you remember what you just said?
Now it's your turn to take responsibility.
Captain.
How can you. Mr. Kim...
Sung. shut up.
I understand...
Let me go alone.
It's not just his fault.
We all voted to come in here.
What's the situation now?
Sung.
Is there something else I need to do?
What does this mean?
Doesn't it want a living sacrifice?
I'm sorry.
I'd like to check the altar.
Can you help me over there?
Please take me near the altar.
But in this case...
I don't think anything will happen.
Have you figured out anything?
No. not yet...
If we wait here. will someone
come to rescue us?
Today is the seventh day
after the dungeon was created.
I think they will take action
before we are rescued.
The portal will be fully open
after seven days.
And that is "Dungeon Break".
Then. the magic beasts will pass through
the portal to the human world.
That's why we must defeat the Boss and
close the portal within the time limit.
This is another purpose
of the raid mission.
If we fail here.
the beasts will run out into the world.
Hello.
Miss Sung.
You come every day.
Mother. it's me again.
Let me tell you. Song-Yi was late today.
She said something kept her.
but she definitely overslept.
And the last nationwide exam...
Please come over here. you two.
This way. we should be able to light
the corresponding number of flames.
Only then will we know what will happen.
The door is open.
Can we go out now?
Can this be a trap...
What is this sound?
The... the statues are coming this way.
What should we do?
Why are they walking towards us?
No!
Joohee. don't close your eyes.
Once we look away. they'll move closer.
It's like the game
we used to play as kids.
Everyone must keep their eyes
fixed on the statues.
No!
- Hey!
- Wait!
Sung. what is this?
The door closed a bit.
but she made it out.
What's going on...
The blue flames will go out over time.
And once someone leaves the altar.
the orange flames will also go out.
The first commandment is "worship".
The second is "praise".
The third is "believe".
That door must be a trap.
It offers false optimism
to us who are in terror.
Perhaps it tests our faith
in God in this way.
So... sorry.
I can't hold on any longer.
- Jungho!
- Hey!
No!
Everyone. don't move!
If anyone else leaves.
it will create a blind spot!
Sung. what does this mean?
Explain it!
Just keep it this way. and don't move
your gaze away from the statue.
The blue flame is a timer.
When it goes out completely.
everyone should be able to escape.
But. Sung...
It's also possible that when the flame
goes out completely. we'll be locked up.
To be honest.
I never thought that you
would be so active as the weakest one.
We can survive until now
all thanks to you.
Mr. Kim...
But you see.
I have family waiting for me.
I don't want to die yet.
I want to go home alive.
I can't hold on any longer.
I'm sorry.
Why...
I won't give up.
I must survive.
I have always survived this way.
You two. leave quickly.
Mr. Song...
I think as long as one person stays.
that door won't close.
Then. I should let the young people
with promising futures leave first.
Joohee. please take care of Sung.
Okay!
Strange...
My leg...
I can't move it.
You've overexerted yourself
when treating Sung.
Mr. Song.
Take Joohee and leave.
What? I said I would stay...
Then who will help Joohee out?
There's no time. hurry up!
No... No... Jinwoo...
Let me stay!
I promised I would take
you out to eat. right?
Use this to buy something to eat.
After I get out.
I'll come to you for
the rest of the money.
How can you still joke...
I'm sorry.
We're really running out of time.
I'll leave her in your care.
Alright.
Great.
Luckily. I am the only one
who's going to die.
If I had known.
I would have bought more insurance.
At least one of you will have
to accompany me on the way.
Come at me!
I'm always the weakest.
People around me always
keep ridiculing me.
But I've tried my best to make it through.
But...
Are you kidding me...
I want to become stronger too.
But I can't.
Despite that.
I've survived up to now in my own way.
Are you...
You can't hold on anymore?
We are all suffering.
You're just justifying yourself.
All the gratitude is just lip service.
It's always the selfish ones
who get all the benefits.
I have a family too.
I want to return home alive too.
"Luckily. I'm the only one
who's going to die?"
Stop it. hypocrite.
Don't...
I don't want to die.
If...
If I could have another chance...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today